Yinon Goldshtein

Email: yinon-g@brainstorm.co.il • Phone: +972 58 447 4099

LinkedIn: <u>yinon-gold</u> ● GitHub: <u>yinon-gold</u>

CS Master's student with a strong background in deep learning and 2 years of development and hands-on experience. Like to keep myself informed with the latest ML technology.

Education

- (Oct 2023 Present) M.Sc. in Computer Science at the Technion.
 Thesis title: Predicting Pathological Response to Radiotherapy Treatment in Colorectal Cancer Patients Using Deep Learning.
- (2018 2023) **B.Sc. in Computer Science at the Technion**, Machine Learning track.

Work Experience

(June 2022 – June 2023) Habana Labs, an Intel Company, Software Engineer Student

- Developed features to a system test framework used by System department teams.
- Implemented component behaviors to be used in future flagship products.

(October 2021 – June 2022) GE Healthcare, Software Engineer Student

• Built a data ETL pipeline for operation data streamed to AWS.

Proiects

- Nomos, Hebrew Verdict Semantic Search Engine Co-founded and key developer of a semantic search engine for verdicts in Hebrew to significantly reduce man-hours in legal research. Utilized search on a vector database of custom embeddings to get relevant results. Got accepted to the Technion's BizTec Startup accelerator.
- NVIDIA Data Loading Library HDF5 Support Developed a plugin for NVIDIA DALI that
 enables creating a custom data loading pipeline for massive HDF5 files.
 Achieved a 40% loading time reduction and 30% memory usage on GPU.
- **CS Technion's Hackathon** Won 2nd place out of 40 groups. Developed in collaboration with Rambam a solution to improve patients' follow-up care after hospital discharge.
- Project in Deep Learning Implemented novel deep learning methods and improved an article on patch adversarial attacks for neural networks in visual odometry, guided by VISTA Lab at Technion's CS faculty.

Leadership Experience

(June 2021 – May 2022) Chairperson of the CS Student Committee, Technion

- Volunteered to lead the student committee consisting of 90 students.
- Directed communication with faculty, day-to-day operations and event organization.

Skills

- Programming languages: Python, C++, Bash, SQL
- Other: Deep Learning, Computer Vision, NLP, Optimization, PyTorch

Languages

Hebrew: Native | English: Fluent